MATIAS EZEQUIEL LEVY



PERSONAL DATA

ADDRESS: Szigony 4, 13/100, Budapest, Hungary.

BIRTH DATE & PLACE: 08/08/1988 - Buenos Aires, Argentina.

PHONE: +4550259948

E-MAIL: ezelevy87@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

October 2021 – Present.

Cognizant – IT Service Desk - Budapest, Hungary.

Spanish & English Service Desk. SAP Management - SAP account creation & Roles assignment. Active Directory - AVD - Citrix - 0365 Administration – Windows

September 2020 - Present.

Solutrip - CEO & Co-founder - Budapest, Hungary

Digital platform for skilled workers who wants to live in Europe. Project Management, generating ideas, developing content and strategies.

January 2020 – August 2020.

Reffen – Operations Team Leader - Copenhagen, Denmark.

Coordinate of events and daily operations. Daily communication and reporting to the management.

September 2018 – March 2019

Firebrand Ltd - Retail Site Specialist - Berlin, Germany.

Harry Potter Official Exhibition - Salesclerk - Cashier - Stock Assistant

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Marketing

University Atlántida Argentina (2013) Average 7.32

Associate Degree in Computer Science

E.E.T Nr. 3 – Argentina (2006) Average 8.33

Python Developer Boot camp

London App Brewery (2022)

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native speaker

English: Fluent

SKILLS

Problem Solving - Proactive - Customer Service - Good diction - Strong knowledge IT Tools

ABOUT ME

I am a 33-year-old professional who has decided to boost his career overseas. With that aim, I left Argentina in 2018 and I started a new life in Europe.

I lived in Germany, Denmark and I am currently resident in Budapest, Hungary.

I am a proactive, reliable person with an excellent ability to quickly solve problems. I am totally committed to teamwork and feel comfortable working on my own as well.

I strongly believe that working in an international environment would add value to my career.

I am passionate about technology, music and sports.

I am available for full time positions as freelancer or onsite positions.